modwedding.com 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy

MOD Enterprise, Inc. (“MODwedding.com”) is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. We recognize that privacy is of utmost importance to users of our products and services, and conduct our business with the recognition that protecting your sensitive personal information is of utmost importance. This privacy policy covers the products and services offered at the MODwedding.com Website (the “Site”) and outlines the types of information we collect, its uses, and steps we take to safeguard it.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our Legal Department at legal(at)modwedding(dot)com. and outlines the types of information we collect, its uses, and steps we take to safeguard it.

### Information We Collect

MODwedding.com is a wedding website creation service provider that allows users (“User(s)”) to manage, organize and share their personal and professional lives online. Accordingly, we collect user submitted personally identifying information and other information specific to the products and services requested or provided. As part of providing you our products and services, we may obtain personal information from the following sources:

  * Information you provide to us on forms that you enter on the Site or that you provide to us in writing.
  * Information that you provide to us by telephone, such as when you contact our Member Care department.
  * Information from third parties, including verification services, payment processing services, and other online and offline sources. It would also include updated address or contact information that we might use to correct our records so that we can communicate with you more easily.
  * Information we receive automatically when you visit our web site. Please see “Cookies and Tracking” below.

The information we collect may include: first name, last name, city, state, address, ZIP code, phone, email address and other information specific to the service requested or provided. If you become a registered subscriber we may collect your credit card information and billing address should you explicitly decide to participate in programs that require this information. Such programs may include becoming a Premium subscriber, and other promotions that MODwedding.com may offer from time to time. We use the information we obtain to develop and deliver our products and services and to fulfill applicable legal requirements. We limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum we require to deliver superior service to our members and to administer our business. Providing your information is voluntary and you can always choose not to provide it by choosing not to use our Site, products, services, or features.

### Cookies and Tracking

Our web servers also use “cookies.” A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer. We use cookies to administer and customize our service and to better understand, on an aggregate basis, how users interact with our Site. If you choose to disable cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site. For example, we require that you have cookies enabled to enroll in our service or to log in to your account. We do not store any personally identifiable information in cookies.

As is true of most web sites, when you visit our Site we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. We gather technical information about your computer such as your IP address, operating system, browser type, pages visited, manner of connection to the Internet, and referring URL. We use this information in aggregate to analyze trends and administer our service. The information that we collect through log files is not tied to personally identifiable information.

We and/or advertising affiliates may employ “tracking pixels” (also referred to as “web beacons”) to count the number of users that visit a page on our Site that includes these tracking pixels. Tracking pixels are used to analyze the effectiveness of advertising campaigns and to better understand the way that users interact with our Site. These tracking pixels do not identify individual users and analysis of data obtained by these tracking pixels is performed on an aggregate basis. The information collected by third advertising affiliates is subject to the privacy policy of the third party.

We also employ a third-party service provider to assist in tracking site usage. This service provider uses cookies and “tracking pixels” to collect information on our behalf about the pages you visit while on our site. This service allows us to better administer the site and our service. The data collected by this service provider does not identify individual users and the analysis of this data is performed on an aggregate basis.

### Third Party Information Sharing

The information collected by MODwedding.com is used in the operation of the Site. In addition, we may share your personal information with third parties that offer related products or services. However, we will only do so with your consent.

We do not share your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We do not share your personal information with other third parties except as permitted or required by applicable law or as described within this privacy policy and including the following:

  * We may disclose personal information about you to third parties when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena or search warrant, or in the course of a legal proceeding. We may also disclose personal information as we believe appropriate to enforce or apply our rights under our agreements with customers, to protect the rights, property or safety of MODwedding.com, our customers and others, including exchanging information for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * In order to provide our services, we may share any of the information we gather about you with agents and service providers to perform functions on our behalf, such as to send email, host videos (if you decide to post one to your account), or process credit card payments. In addition, address information may be shared with a service provider to determine geographic information. These service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * If there is a change of control in MODwedding.com’s business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise), its customer information could be sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information-handling practices as described in this statement, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on our Site, and you will have a choice as to whether your existing information is used in a new manner.  
Choices Available to You

MODwedding.com provides users the ability to opt-out of receiving email communications from us. If you wish to cease future communications, you can opt-out by using the link on the bottom of any email that you receive from MODwedding.com or, if you are a registered member, by visiting the Profile & Settings section of your account.

MODwedding.com reserves the right to send you specific administrative notices that are required by law, regulation, or as needed to service your account. Administrative notices also include notifications of new messages or job postings in your area and responses to jobs that you have posted. You may not opt-out of receiving these administrative emails. If you wish to no longer receive administrative emails from MODwedding.com you must close your account through the Profile & Settings section of the site.

### Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may update this information by logging into your account and accessing the Account Settings section of your account. If you no longer wish to participate in our service you may contact MODwedding.com Member Care at membercare(at)modwedding(dot)com and request that your account be closed.

### How We Protect Your Information

MODwedding.com is committed to earning and keeping your trust and we understand the need to keep your information secure and private. You should never share your MODwedding.com password with anyone. If you feel your password has been compromised, you should change it immediately by logging into your account and accessing the Profile & Settings section of your account. After you have finished using our Site, you should log out of your MODwedding.com account and exit your browser.

### Privacy Policy Updates

This Privacy Policy may change, from time to time, due to changes on our Site, legal developments, business factors and ever-changing technology. Notifications to changes of our Privacy Policy will be posted on our Site, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Contact for Privacy Related Issues

If you have any questions on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:  
Email: legal(at)modwedding(dot)com
